pinkxxx.co.uk 2012-09-19

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Pinkxxx.co.uk values the privacy of our visitors/customers greatly and takes every known precaution to guard the information we collected from unauthorized use. The following is a detailed explanation for the privacy policy of Pinkxxx

####  WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

TinyDeal believes it is important for you to know what types of information we collect when you visit our site. We have various methods to collect information. The following is a list of the information we collect: Email, Name, Street Address, Post Code, City, Country, Telephone Number, and password.

####  WHY DO WE COLLECT THIS INFORMATION?

We use this information in order to serve the needs of our customers. We need to know who you are in order to verify the credit card information you have sent us. We collect several pieces of personal information from you in order to complete this verification process. The non-personal information that we collect from you is used in order to offer you better service and to make your experience with our site more enjoyable. Any information that we may inadvertently collect from you, that does not serve one of these reasons stated above, is immediately purged from our system.

####  WHO HAS ACCESS TO MY INFORMATION?

Only those employees that are responsible for handling your account have access to your information. Additionally, employees in our technical department may have access to your information in order to conduct routine checks on the integrity of our system and in order to perform necessary maintenance work. In order to process your credit card we have to consult with an out side credit card processing company. These processing companies are regulated by the banking industry and must meet certain security requirements in order to be in business. The processing companies will have access to your credit card information, billing address, name, and possibly your telephone number. The processing company will communicate with the issuing bank of your credit card in order to get final approval to charge your credit card for the product or services we are providing for you. Should you choose to receive additional information regarding one of our services or products, we may pass your email address to one of our partners who offers similar products or services that you might be interested in. Additionally, judicial requests by a duly authorized court will require us to divulge certain information regarding your account should that situation arise. Finally, should our company ever be bought or sold, your account information would then become the property of the new owner/entity.

####  CAN I CORRECT OR REMOVE INFORMATION FROM YOUR SITE?

You always have the option to view your account to make sure the information we have collected from you is indeed correct. You also have the option of removing any information from your account that you wish to keep private. However, please note that removing certain information such as your email address, contact information, and the like may greatly hinder our ability to effectively provide the service or products you have requested. We recommend, that you contact us first to discuss which information you may remove without interrupting the quality of service we intend to provide for you.

####  NOTICE OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time.
